The worst monsters are of our own making
Savage Flowers is a thriller, horror film directed by Brad Watson.
Set in an infected world where the children are carriers - a young orphan finds sanctuary in a
ramshackle foster home but she soon discovers it's not the world outside that she should fear.
It's the girls she's inside with.
Lucy, played by Roxanne McKee.
Rose, played by Olivia-Mai Barrett.
Lily, played by Maddie Mills.
Rebekah, played by Connie Jenkins-Greig.
Ada, played by Meesha Garbett.
Iris, played by Romanie Jija-Wakeham.
Savage Flowers is a 2025 British thriller film directed by Brad Watson
from a screenplay by Ben Charles Edwards and Dominic Wells.
It premiered at the inaugural Cine International Film Festival (CIFF).
The tone is dark and intense.